Avinash Yadav

Faridabad, Haryana, India



ayy296i3ehyx@gmail.com



8368243559



linkedin.com/in/avinash-yadav-bb8057212

Summary

I BCA graduate enthusiasm. my past experience was completely based on learning and training on practical technical things .Now currently I search for reputed company for gaining practical experience development. I currently doing full stack development training at ducat IT training school Noida.

Currently, I am about to finish my final semester/year at college. In the course of 3 years during graduation, I have been taught a lot of things. Now I try to find better opportunity so I can showcase my talent and prove my skills.

Experience

DUCAT Full Stack Engineer

Ducat Education

Apr 2023 - Present (5 months)

Here, I am currently doing offline training on python full stack development on sat-sun since April 2023

Python Programming

CipherByte Technologies

Aug 2023 - Present (1 month)

completing python programming task like mastermind game and rock paper scissor game

Web Development Intern

CodSoft

Jul 2023 - Aug 2023 (2 months)

I completed a task on web development like landing Page ,Portfolio , Calculator webpage development

Django web development

O(1) Coding Club

Jul 2023 - Present (2 months)

the internship is based on Django web application development .Here,I am getting practical training in Django and help me develop a django application

Education



Bachelor of computer application, Computer Software and Media Applications Oct 2020 - Apr 2023

Ducat IT training school Noida

Python full stack developer Apr 2023 - Present

Licenses & Certifications

- Al for 2.0 GUVI Geek Networks, IITM Research Park 2w0xzZ69i6y2013p9e
- python GUVI Geek Networks, IITM Research Park FB57812Rt9V68E7ou5
- Data Science Internshala Trainings
 9D0423AA-8A7A-76DD-4B7D-572CDE0EDDA2

Skills

Python (Programming Language) • Django • MySQL • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • C (Programming Language) • Web Development